Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - Facilities, 1979-1981 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: New Line Cinema, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Miscellaneous, 1979-1986 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Hospital Connection, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Long Range Planning Committee, 1979-1987 (Box 18)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1971-1980 (Box 18)
  - Policy/Constitution, 1980 (Box 18)
  - University Union Board, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Organizational Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Final Reports Concerning Student-Run Organizations undated, circa 1980s (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Needs, undated, 1980s (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Logos and Graphics, undated, 1980s (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Pyramid Files undated, circa 1980s (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, Spring 1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, Fall 1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, Spring 1981 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Life on the Quad [student-created soap opera], undated, late 70s/early 80s (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Production Ideas, 1977-1984 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Budgets and Finances, 1976-1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: TV Symposium - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Evaluations, 1977-1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: West Glen Films, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Outside Programming, 1976-1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Programming Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Outside Programming, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Joint Programming/Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1976-1981 (Box 18)
  - University Union Board: General, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - University Union Board, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Black Student Alliance/Black History Month, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Retreat Fall 1980 [Emerald Isle], Fall 1980 (Box 18)
  - Advertising Information, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Policy, 1973-1981 (Box 18)
  - Joint Programming Committee/Executive Committee Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Programming Committee: Reports/Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Finance: Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Finance: General, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Programming Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - General Records, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Finance: Budgets, 1981-1982/1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: EMI Music, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Tape Rights, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: ASDU, 1976-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Summer Plans, Cable Manual, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Canadian Film Board Film Series, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Broadcast Schedules, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Trinity Zone undated, circa 1980s (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Structure/Policy, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cable 13: Outside Programming, 1980-1982 (Box 18)
  - John Anderson, September 16, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Mardi Gras, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Facilities Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Broadway at Duke: "Getting My Act Together", February 18, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Major Speakers: General Records, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - A.B. Meacham, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Galleries Committee: Sandra Milroy, April 20-June 5, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Elizabeth Cate Pringle, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Joan Gessner, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Gregory, Donna, and Bill Haneman, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Galleries Committee: Tina Guild, April 20-June 5, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Ken Huang, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Galleries Committee: Atlantic Art Reproduction, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Bill Bamberger, March 13-April 10, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Missie Dickens, 1982 (Box 18)
  - William T. Gambling, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Springfest, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Broadway at Duke Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Fred Tullis, 1983 (Box 18)
  - English Beat, March 26, 1983 (Box 18)
  - The Go-Go's, September 15, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Ben Vereen, November 5, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Caroline Wang and Kate Rhodenbraugh, Brown Gallery, April 12-May 4, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Galleries Committee: Student Juried Art Show Forms, November, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Mike Cross, October 8, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Galleries Committee: Winnett, Merry Moor, November 11, 1982-January 1, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Major Attractions Policy, Revised February, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Programming Council/Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Summer Programming, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Union Retreats, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Calendar Photographs, ca. 1981-1984 (Box 19)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Retreat, September 11, 1981 (Box 19)
  - DUU Finance Statement, Various Monthly, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Financial Report, February 3, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Storage Space: Flowers, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Grateful Dead, 1982 (Box 19)
  - CEN, circa 1982 (Box 19)
  - News Bureau Page, circa 1982 (Box 19)
  - Native American Awareness Week and Judy McDade, circa 1982 (Box 19)
  - Triangle Dance Guild Artist Roster, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Association of College, Univeristy and Community Arts Administrators (ACUCAA) Miscellaneous Materials, 1982 (Box 19)
  - ACUCAA General Records, 1982 (Box 19)
  - ACUCAA Marketing Workshop, 1982 (Box 19)
  - ACUCAA 26th Annual conference, December 16-20, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes (including materials from the Finance (Box 19)
  - Committee Program Council; University Board), 1981 (Box 19)
  - Program Council: Minutes (includes budgets), 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82, Miscellaneous Records, February, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82 Symposium - Miscellaneous Records (intro, Chronicle articles, schedules, program formats, advertising), 1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82, Miscellaneous Records, cont'd (funding), 1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82, Miscellaneous Records, cont'd, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82, Miscellaneous Records, cont'd (Faculty relations, pre-symposium events, membership, etc), 1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82 - Federation Involvement, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: STEP 82, February 1982 (Box 19)
  - Summer Programming, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Programs, Clippings, etc, 1950s-1982 (Box 19)
  - Chronicle Board, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - AAUS Convention, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Woven Treasures, Charles Llewellyn, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Frieda Dean - West, September 4-25, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Insurance Coverage of Art Exhibits, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Fall Exhibits, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Student Shows, Fall 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Jane Goco, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Ken Huang, June, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Alex Harris, November, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Cynthia Camlin and Ann Clark, December, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Joseph Walentiny, January, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Joan Gessner, January-February, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Paul Kwilecki, February, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Todd Cull, February, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: John Szarkowski, March, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Indian Awareness Week, March, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: DADA, March 30-April 10, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Stephanie B. Carleton, August 20-September 30, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Rejects, Spring 1981 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Jacob Roquet and Helen Smith, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Galleries Committee: Missie Dickens, October, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Update, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Photos and Playbills, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Musician Maria Rhines - Violinist, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Click 'n' Cloggers, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Mornings at Seven/Mimi Garrard, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Barbara Cook, October 9, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Sugar Babies, October 29, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: St. Mark's Gospel, November 3, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Children of a Lesser God, November 12, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: A Christmas Carol, December 8, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Mornings at Seven, January 29, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: One Mo' Time, March 2, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Richard II, April 19, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Finance, Vendors, and Policies, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Facilities Committee: General Records, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - General Records: Programming Manual, Minutes, etc, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Retreat, Fall 1981 (Box 20)
  - Springfest '82: Tax Agreement Forms, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Programming Committee: Miscellaneous Records, circa 1982 (Box 20)
  - University Union Board, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Reports [various committees], 1981-1982 (Box 20)
  - Program Council, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Finance, 1981-1982 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: Vernon Pratt, January 7, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Special Events Committee: Oktoberfest, October 2, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Special Events Committee: Square Dance, October 18, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Special Events Committee: Bands for Spring, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Special Events Committee: All-Nighter, March 19, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Special Events Committee: Springfest, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Publicity Committee: The Happening, September 5, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Publicity Committee: Bands, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Publicity Committee: Bernie Kenerson, February 27, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Finance Committee: Committees Budgets, pre-1984 (Box 20)
  - Student Activities Brochure, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Proposed Budgets, 1982 (Box 20)
  - WDUK, circa 1982 (Box 20)
  - Union Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Triangle Dance Guild (Coordinating Committee), circa 1977-1983 (Box 20)
  - Triangle Dance Guild, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Trustees Monthly Report, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Tickets (off-campus in Bryan Center), 1983 (Box 20)
  - Family Night at Duke, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Mary Lou Williams Cultural Center, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Sunday Brunches, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Minutes, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: Jeannette Oliver, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: Abraham Rattner, Esther Gentle Rattner, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: A.B. Meacham, October, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: Fred Tullis, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: Marson, November 19, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: Applications, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: Miscellaneous Symposiums, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: Miscellaneous Records, Symposium '83, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: Symposium '83 Finances, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: Symposium '83 Administrative Files, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Symposium Committee: "Narcissism in an Age of Disengagement", February, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Galleries Committee: Diana Parrish Cull, circa 1983 (Box 20)
  - Summer Programming, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Performing Arts Committee: PDQ Bach, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: History, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: College Cable Network, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Dramatic Productions, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Editing Manual (Jeff Morrill), 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: General Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: EMI Music, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Inventory, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Minutes (Task Force), 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Satellite Communications, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Telecommunications Project, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Telecommunications Technologies (Bill Garrison), 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Campus Entertainment Network, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: 3D Movie "Gorilla At Large", 1982 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Cable Van, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Donations, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Durham Cablevision Hook-up, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Needs, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Kurlander, Carl, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Video Syndication Rights (Telecommunications), 1983 (Box 20)
  - Cable 13: Warner Brothers, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Yearlook Enterprises, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Yearlook Articles, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Video Yearlook, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Facilities, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Privilege Cards, 1979-1982 (Box 20)
  - Policy, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Programming Committee: Agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Programming Committee: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Programming Council: Matters and Materials, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Official Information, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Xerox Copier at Info. Desk (inc. letter from Senator Jesse Helms), 1983 (Box 20)
  - Union Dinner, Spring 1983 (Box 20)
  - Minutes and Memoranda, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Programming Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes and Agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Programming Council/Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Key Deposits - Bryan Center; Office Space (Box 20)
  - Allocation, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Non-Smoking Policy Guidance, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Bryan Center, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Food Service, 1972-1983 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Facilities (inc. display cases), 1982 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Report, undated, circa 1980s (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Bryan Center Space Allocations, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Agendas, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Memoranda, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Facilities Committee: Miscellaneous/General Records, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Reynolds Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: LPTV Task Force, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Finance: General, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Finance: General, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: History, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Task Force Minutes, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Electronic Arts Intermix, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - Facilities: General, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Facilities: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Finance: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts: Budget/Finance, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Programming: Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, etc., 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Cooking, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Satellite Video (Telecomm.), 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Satellite Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Editing Manual, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Documentary - Peet Mining Task Force, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Facilities: Miscellaneous/General, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Production Handbook [David Swearington], 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Production Personnel, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Executive Committee Meetings, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Fuqua Video Facilities, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Progress Report, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Inventory, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13: History (Walter Deane), 1983 (Box 21)
  - Programming Council Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Finance Committee Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Union Newsletter, 1982 (Box 21)
  - MCA Scholarship Applicants, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cable 13 Mission, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cameron Gym Floor Damage (Go-Go's Concert), 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Executive Secretary, University Union Board, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Union Board Correspondence, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Executive Committee Members and Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Interaction Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Programming for University Bars, General Records, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Programming for University Bars, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Special Events: General Records, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: General Records, bulk 1983 (Box 21)
  - Broadway at Duke: "Tintype", September 29, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Broadway at Duke: Intimate PDQ Bach, October 12, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Broadway at Duke: Showtimes, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Alan Cranston, October 22, 1982 (Box 21)
  - John Fitzharris, Movie Magic, March 1, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Abbie Hoffman, October 26, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Steve Bell (ABC), January 27, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Facilities Committee: Minutes, 1973-1983 (Box 21)
  - Facilities Committee: Office Space, Telephone, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - A Christmas Carol, December 2, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Broadway at Duke: Colored People's Time, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Daniel Yergin, April 13, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Special Events Committee: Flying Pigs, circa 1983 (Box 21)
  - Retreat Spring, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Finance, 1983 (Box 21)
  - NACA, February, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Copier Prices, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous Records, circa 1983 (Box 21)
  - Publicity, 1983 (Box 21)
  - All-Nighter in the U-Center, circa 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Summer Programming, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Monthly Budgets, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - DUU Program, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Interaction Committee, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Facilities, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Special Events: Christmas Tree Lighting, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Durham Crop Walk, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Cameron Reservations, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - The GUIDE Magazine, circa 1983 (Box 21)
  - Budget Requests, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - Final Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - NACA National Convention, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Lunchtime Series, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Agnes of God, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Agnes of God, January 31, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Crimes of the Heart (2 folders), January 19, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat (2 folders), February 21, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Marcel Marceau, February 22, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Marcel Marceau, February 27, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Broadway at Duke Midwinter Series, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - Galleries Committee: Hely Lima, March 23, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Galleries Committee: Pat Shelton, April, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Galleries Committee: Joan Smiley Durden, April, 1984 (Box 21)
  - Galleries Committee: Kate Peteroff, undated, circa 1983-1984 (Box 21)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Facilities: Space Allocation, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Retreat (Fall), 1983 (Box 37)
  - Homecoming, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, etc., 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Advisory Board, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Budget, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Constitution, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: History (Walter Deane), 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Development, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Documentary - Peat Mining Task Force, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Inventory, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Executive Committee Meetings, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Home Box Office (Telecommunications), 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Insurance (Libel & Slander), 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Production Handbook [David Swearington], 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Production Personnel, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Proposals, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Satellite Video (Telecomm.), 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Teleconference Center Construction Guidelines, 1983 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: DUAA, 1983-1984; 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Development, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Telecommunications Project, 1984 (Box 37)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, etc., 1983-1985 (Box 37)
  - Finance: Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Programming Council, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Constitutional Revision, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Minutes, various committees, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Donations, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Galleries: General Information, 1982-1984 (Box 37)
  - Reunion Activities, June, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: General, 1981-1985 (Box 37)
  - Interaction Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 37)
  - Homecoming, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Galleries: Ad Handbook, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Campus Entertainment Network, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Jerry Garcia, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Programming, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Major Attractions: Miscellaneous/General, 1980-1985 (Box 37)
  - Performing Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: General Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: AT&T Project, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Bryan Center Proposed Film/Video Center, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Bryan Center Space, circa 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: General Rogers Visit, October 18, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Facilities, bulk 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Facilites: General, 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Jazz Festival, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Cameron, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Bryan Center Video Screening Room, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Cable Cast Football, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Officer Information/Applications, pre-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Summer Leadership Program, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Sloan Speakers, circa 1985 (Box 37)
  - Constitutional Revision, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Executive Committee Meetings, 1979; 1984 (Box 37)
  - Finance: Reports, pre-1985 (Box 37)
  - Finance: General, 1982-1985 (Box 37)
  - Cable 13: Cable TV General Literature, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Day, Tracy, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Video Alternatives Committee (VAC), 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: Video Yearbook, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: World Communications, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Policy: Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Programming: Schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Room Usage, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Finance: Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Finance: Audit, June, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Tax Agreement Forms: Springfest '83, Folk Fest '83, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Yearlook, circa 1983 (Box 22)
  - Video Yearlook, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Yearlook: Video Alternatives Committee, 1984 (Box 22)
  - American Pictures, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - MCI - Call Saver, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Publicity, 1983 (Box 22)
  - "Do You Wants?", 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Copy Center, circa 1980s (Box 22)
  - Facilities Committee: Bryan Center Birthday Celebration, February 27, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Scott, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Form Descriptions, circa 1980s (Box 22)
  - Minutes, Fall, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Budget Proposals, 1983-1985 (Box 22)
  - Provost's Agreement, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Retreat: Emerald Isle, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Long-Range Development, mid-1980s (Box 22)
  - Cable 13: General Records, 1983 (Box 22)